i told y'all niggas i told yes i told y'all
but you don't hear me though said i told y'all niggas but you don't hear me though
tell them in the comments y'all tell them tell them tell them in the comments while i sing my song
said i told y'all niggas but you don't hear me though but you don't hear me though
but y'all don't hear me though but you don't hear me though i told y'all i told y'all that them
buddies over there in philadelphia was not legit told y'all niggas i told y'all
ricky said my next tour should be called i told y'all i told y'all i told y'all
them was not some panthers i told y'all they was using that name on some fraudulent shit i told
y'all didn't i i told y'all said i told y'all my god i told y'all the same way
that i told you that your man's biden wasn't going to be the presidential candidate
and folks reacted the same way you're just told y'all niggas i told y'all niggas kamala harris was
not going to win and the only way she could was in order was by her being anti-genocide
told y'all niggas i told y'all niggas
and i told y'all niggas that them folks were not black panthers hold on are y'all saying lions are
they calling themselves the black lions it wasn't an easy declaration rcc maybe it was for you talking
to your little friends but it wasn't when you're a public figure with 2.3 million followers it wasn't
an easy declaration i actually had my entire life smeared for it i actually lost work for it
so no it wasn't an easy declaration they're calling themselves the black lion well you know what
good be something new and get your weight up in a legitimate organic way period that's it
that's how it should have been from jump it is absolutely
disingenuous to do anything else and let me also say this
some people are like well it doesn't matter and i'm not that i'm not that person who
um is like i don't care where the money comes from as long as we get to do what we need to do
i'm not that girl so like i don't relate to um oh it doesn't matter if they're dishonest as long as
they're doing the job so you know that's it because i don't believe that you can be honest in your work
if you're starting from a dishonest place the black lions of international solidarity fabulous
layla layla i need a recording of layla singing i told y'all nigga
i need that hathaway stank on it i don't think y'all really understand what it is like
to be constantly harangued and harassed and then be constantly correct i don't i don't think y'all
understand but baby so i just wanted to come on here and um and gloat they didn't take nothing
they didn't take nothing because it got called out and cut up quick before it could go too far
it got called out and shut up quick and you know i moved by spirit so it wasn't until spirit told me
to say something that i said something that's a dog that's jordie normacita what the hell is you
on about y'all love to talk about unity and divisiveness and all type of shit but so many
of y'all think everything is divisive it's like sapphire my hair has been locked for like a year and a half
so just wanted to that was my gal i ain't never seen val's face but i feel like i would still know
her if she was sitting next to me on the bus just by vibes so i just wanted to come on here
and tell y'all that i be knowing to remind you baby if it's bewildering it's because it's not true
the truth is a short route that's what i'm gonna leave y'all with
this is what i'm gonna leave y'all with the truth is a short route you can live by that
it don't take long for the truth to be explained it don't take long for the truth to be vetted
so anytime you find someone giving you a long ass explanation you can already know
this ain't the truth anytime you find somebody telling you oh it's too long it's it's too complicated
it's because it ain't the truth the truth is a short route somebody needs to be vetted that shit can
happen in 24 hours max the truth is a short route live by that and you will save yourself so much time
so much time
so that's what i want to that's what i'm leaving you with tonight okay the truth is a short route
next time you find yourself in a conversation with somebody and you trying to get to the truth and
they doing all type of rah rah shish boom bah cut it cut it because the truth should usually be
explained in tops three sentences tops tops people trying to tell you about palestine and all this is
complicated no it ain't no it ain't quick this is a colonial project this is a settler colonial project
one sentence oh the democrats you know they have they they're not able to do the job because
the democrats are paid for by the same people as the republicans and they serve the same purpose
to disenfranchise the populace two sentence two sentences
short route so live by that practice that by the way because you got to practice it too
a lot of times y'all be coming in my comments with these god dang essays and i'm like
if it's more than three sentences i'm not reading it i'm not reading it i i really
miss vividly vivid genuine question who the hell do you think you are
like y'all be on here with no picture and no name just running your yap who are you
like genuine fuck out of here you should do that if you did this like man you are not a person
you don't have a name and you don't got a face get out of here you can't see the comments because
instagram has me shadow banned and now you got some bitch in here named miss kina i am a big mouth
with no traction seeking to go viral what have you done for the community i think sometimes y'all
just be saying shit just because you want to hear me talk about what i've done for the community
because you're like you know what we need to hear it again like i think sometimes you just
be saying it because you're just like i feel like i miss i i feel like i just want to hear it one more
time i'll be asking that why y'all be saying that
thank you renata call it rage bait k avery i'ma call it i'ma call it um what am i gonna call it
it's not rage bait it's it's um it's flavor flourishing they just want my flavors to flourish
so they just want me to to really just be like oh my god let me tell y'all one more time
you know what i you know what's the one thing i've i've really one one major thing that i have done for
the community something really consistent major thing that i have done for the community
is that's what i did for the community is i told y'all niggas okay all right that's what i did
shit so you're welcome you're welcome that's right vibrant that's right i'll be at a protest
on january 31st that's where i'ma be man listen
coming on here to have a laugh but my neck is burning so let me get off
this phone y'all there is water in that mug i don't drink the only thing i really drink if you
if at all is bailey's and that's when i'm in grenada only only my hair's been locked since
september 2025 no september 2026 september 2026 so god bless the black lions may they be supported
if they are true and that goes for all organizations that seek to stand in the gap
that seek to provide an outlet for folks and an inroad for change
okay however in a time of great dis uh dissemination of disinformation we must
i said 2024 my hair has been locked since 2024 september 2024
in a time of great dissemination what are y'all talking about someone asked me how long has my
hair been locked my hair has been locked since september 2024
oh well y'all saying 2025 that's what i meant 2024 um
but uh again when we are in a time of disinformation it is imperative that we
anchor ourselves to a demand for truth and transparency in all corners in all works
okay that is something that is not done lightly why the fuck are y'all still talking about this
how can my hair be locked in september 2026 it was clearly just a misstatement get over it move on
like move on weirdos so there is no and and again this also leads back to
or leads forward to your spirituality and your soul what are you grounded in and if you're lying to
yourself then you can't care about the government or about non-profits or about anybody lying to you
really you can't if you're lying to yourself it is your first obligation to be honest to you
before you expect anybody else to be honest with you
i couldn't give two dams about the memphis grizzlies i don't care about the nba
whatsoever i don't care about none of these rich niggas who ain't saying nothing about nothing
if that's what you're asking okay i'm grounded in the earth that's what i'm grounded in i'm grounded
in the soil i don't care nothing about none of these rich billionaire niggas who don't say shit
about nothing they play the ball they throw the ball they hit the ball they catch the ball
like i don't you know i don't care if they was really bad about it they'd be like we not taking
the goddamn court unless ice leaves the goddamn city like that's what that that's really what they
should be on of course the wnba been speaking up they stay speaking up wnba always been bad about it
riding riding irving is an anomaly you know sean takai he's he's an anomaly you know that's the that's
the young homie right there he's an anomaly and like you can't base an entire structure on an anomaly
there's always going to be an anomaly that's just kind of the the way it works beyonce quiet
what she here's the thing about beyonce beyonce ain't never talked about anything she barely talked
about her own music someone in here said it's not the player's job to get rid of ice it ain't oh so
we only doing things that we're paid for we're only doing things that are our job now i just just just
so i understand why would i want to interview rappers up today why these niggas can't rap okay
the chat is the chat is is chatting ice is black people's business me putting my body outside to fight
ice is not gonna happen thank you tito lane wait thank you the toya lynn i hope you told them
she be knowing i'm reading the comments what do i think defense against ice looks like
have you not been seeing what they doing in minnesota that's not core mega mega core mega is it
no i'm not frozen i'm just reading the comments check this out i'm not gonna tell black people to stay
home i'm just saying don't expect me to okay so it's not core mega all right i'm just not
i i i i listen it's the same way that's like don't expect black people to educate white people
on how to be anti-racist but if that's what you want to do you have every right to like that's all
i'm saying there's many other ways to so to support the movement oh baby qatarie that's what
qatarie did i see it qatarie did i see it i called it like a cordless phone hello
i told y'all niggas he lucky i didn't post the corny ass dms he had sent me
good night y'all